spelthorne.gov.uk 2014-05-14

# Privacy Policy - Spelthorne Borough Council

You are here:

  1. [Home](http://www.spelthorne.gov.uk/home)
  2. / Privacy Policy 

## Cookies 

If you are a user with general public and anonymous access, the Spelthorne Borough Council website does not store or capture personal information. We automatically collect the following information: 

  * date and time of access 
  * originating IP address   
This does not allow us to identify you or store/capture personal information, but merely logs the user's IP address that is automatically recognised by the web server and ensures that the web server is able to send the required information to the requesting computer. 
  * type of browser   
This tells us the browser software visitors use to our access our website (e.g. Internet Explorer, Netscape Navigator, Mosaic etc.) 
  * URL of the referring page   
Information on how you access our website. For example via a search on a search engine or by directly typing in our website address 
  * Page requested   
What pages were visited during the visitor session

This information allows Spelthorne Borough Council to evaluate how visitors are using our website, including the number of visitors and page views. We cannot and will not use this information to identify you personally. 

**How cookies are used**

We do not use cookies for collecting user information and we will not collect any information about you except that required for system administration of our web server. For example, we may use a cookie for the administration of our survey software, to prevent multiple responses from the same PC/person. A cookie is a simple text file that allows a web site to store information on your computer's hard disk and retrieve it the next time you visit the site. Cookies are not programmes and therefore cannot harm your computer. 

This privacy statement only covers the Spelthorne Borough Council website. This statement does not cover links within this site to other websites. 

  * Print this page 
  * Published 22 August 2013, 11.22AM
